This is how I'll become.
Supreme Commander!
A hero!
This is my story!
All
right.
I was watching my dreams.
It wasn't as high as I could!
I wanted to see that.
That's when you were me?
I was connected.
How much is it?
I'm going to move now.
I'm going to come back.
I must,
I will do this moment!
I will set the light.
I will never change. I will never change.
I will never change.
Good work.
We put those monsters in their place.
Well spotted.
Attaboy, Yuki.
She complimented me.
This is great.
At this rate, I'm bound to get stronger.
If I'm lucky, I'll get strong
enough to protect Ms. Kyoka.
So, what kind of reward
is this supposed to be?
I haven't sustained
any injuries, you know.
I'm not so sure myself.
It's appropriate for Nei, but doing this
type of thing with me is a waste of time.
Huh? No way!
That's completely untrue! It's fine!
Fine, then.
I just don't understand your appetites.
You pervert.
Wow, our Yuki's making more progress.
He follows my orders to a T,
seeking out the most efficient method
on his own before taking action.
That's fantastic, Yuki.
Oh, no, it's nothing.
Aw, you're so adorable in
your blushing little sleigh.
Oh, Miss Tenka!
Commander Izumo, don't you think you
should be heading back to your dorm?
It'll be fine.
You really are incredible.
Good job today.
Have you always been this talented?
Hey! Knock it off!
Well, I wouldn't say I'm talented exactly,
but my big sister taught me a
lot when I was a little kid.
Big sister? Oh, yeah.
You said your big sister
was pretty cool, right?
Oh, you must really admire her. Yeah.
Tell us what she was like?
Hey, Wakura!
I don't like that you're
always ignoring me, idiot!
You think I'm stupid?
It's cause you're always
saying mean things to me!
Come on, kid, play nice
with my little brother.
Get your hands off my brother! Huh?
Ha!
Is that your sister?
Yuki, are you...?
I learned a move or two from
playing pro wrestler with you.
I'm not some little wimp, okay?
Now that's my precious little brother.
You get an A+.
You'll regret this.
This calls for a celebration.
Come on, let's go get a treat.
I'll pay.
That's just the way she was.
She sounds like a good sister.
She was training you and
you didn't even know it.
Younger siblings sure do
have it rough sometimes, huh?
I think we figured out
what makes Yuki tick!
Yuki, take the rest of
the evening off. Thanks.
I'll take a bath and then a nap.
Go home, Tenka.
I suppose it's getting late.
I'll see you later.
All this talk of big sisters
is making Ney feel jealous.
So we're the only ones
without siblings, huh?
I was the youngest in my family,
but everyone liked to spoil me.
That sounds about right.
I detect someone in danger!
Four kilometers south! Himari!
Shushu! On the devil! Right!
D .D .F. in the house!
Relax, we got this!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Thanks for that!
Kimari!
Coco knows how to pack a punch.
I caught some demon defense force.
Now, let's make him suffer.
Another humanoid?
Hang it on!
I'm gonna blast you in the next week!
Kimari, are you good? Yeah.
I blocked it in the nick of time.
Hey, that's not bad.
Hold on! Huh?
Your name is Coco, correct?
Huh?
How did you know my name?
Wait a minute, is that your Peach ability?
Uh, no.
You said Coco knows how to pack a punch.
The Supreme Commander of the Demon Defense
Force is willing to
negotiate with your kind.
Will you hear us out? Ha! Dream on!
I'm gonna destroy you!
So many cuts and bruises.
We've been fighting Shuki
left and right lately. Hmm?
Well, at least my muscles
are coming along nicely.
Keep getting those gains, my dude.
All right!
I'm coming in!
Hey, Miss Kyoka!
We're under attack.
Time to transform. Wait!
You mean, like, right this minute?
Get a move on.
Shushu and Himari are in trouble.
My bullets can't pierce it!
What do you think?
Kuma's got mega-tough armor!
Huh?
I also have the ability to adapt!
Cancel ability!
It's a free-for-all.
This ought to be fun.
Take this!
Nice.
I wiped out all of the pint-sized Shuki.
Now I just need a backup, Himari.
It's...
wielding a weapon?
Now, it's one of them.
You came out to play.
Dodge it!
Yuki!
Quit building! Right!
Objective complete.
No way!
They... vanished?
Really?
They took him?
Yuki must have been their
target from the very beginning.
I guess that explains why the
humanoids showed up only to retreat.
They had already accomplished their goal.
Yuki.
Commander!
Back to the dorm.
Your wounds need medical attention first.
We'll take a quick
breather and regroup after.
Where are you?
Big sis?
Huh?
That feels really good.
Settle down and keep yourself still.
You'll be better in no
time, so bear with me, okay?
That's right.
I remember getting captured.
And now I've woken up to the
enemy licking my whole body.
Wait, first things first.
During the fight when she
yelled my name, I knew it.
That was my sister.
Hey, can you?
Hey, stop squirming.
I'm trying to be thorough.
Am I being assaulted by the enemy?
What do I do?
All righty, looks like we're in
the clear. How's Yuki? Is he awake?
Uh... Hey, Alba.
You're just in time for...
Damn it, Coco!
What the hell would possess
you to strip my brother naked?!
Such an ugly misunderstanding.
Huh?
He was naked when his
transformation was broken.
He also had several injuries.
That's why Coco was healing him.
Beauty of the self-sacrificing sort.
I did it because he's your brother!
I wanted to heal every
left scratch on him!
Now that you mention it, all
of my scratches are gone.
It's my saliva.
It's got medicinal properties.
She did say you would
be better in no time.
I'm so sorry, Coco.
Thanks for helping.
I'll treat you to something yummy.
Always one to reward.
It really is you.
It's been too long.
You're all grown up now, Yuki.
You were alive.
The entire time.
You'll never be able to
get rid of me that easily.
Big sis.
I guess it all worked out.
Sibling love, it's a beautiful thing.
But wait a sec, why do you look like that?
You're the one not wearing any pants.
My, my, you really have grown.
Go ahead and put these on.
We'll take a walk outside afterwards.
Given the location and how we all appear,
it would be faster just to show you.
We refer to it as the Hidden Village.
There aren't any peach trees in the area,
so the Demon Defense Force doesn't
come poking around out here.
So then there are others
who look just like you.
About 20 people call this place home.
All are former humans.
Like the three of us.
I'm Coco Zenibako!
I now own you know.
Oh, so Shuki start off as humans?
Well, those things are
full-blooded monsters.
We happen to be a special case.
It's a half-human,
half-monster kind of situation.
An accident caused us to end up like this,
but our souls are still human like yours.
It's a pretty nice setup.
And from now on, you
and I can live together!
Don't worry!
You won't have to deal with being
treated like a slave anymore!
Whoa, just slow down a minute!
There's no reason for
you to hide, big sis!
You're a human!
Talk to the Demon Defense Force!
They'll protect you!
That's not an option!
The Demon Defense Force is our enemy!
They enslaved you, and with the way their
hierarchy works, we can never be allies.
A battle is inevitable.
They were friendly up until a minute ago.
What the hell happened?
Are you okay?
You're really lucky the
wound isn't very deep.
I think this should fix it.
Yeah, I'll be just fine.
Besides, I'm way more worried
about how Yuki is doing.
I can't act like a whiny baby.
Hey, Nei!
Did you find him? Mm-mm.
I asked the other squads to
help me look, but no luck. Ugh.
I'll try widening the search.
Good idea.
I wonder what the commander is doing.
She's been holed up inside her
room ever since we got back home.
The Supreme Commander has issued an order
that no one is to attack the humanoids,
right?
Maybe that's why.
Yeah, but while we're just
sitting around, Yuki might...
The fact they abducted him tells me that
they've got a specific goal in mind.
I'm sure he's safe, so don't worry.
The Commander will come
up with a plan of her own.
Obeying someone other than me?
He's in big trouble when he gets back.
Big Sis, what's going on?
How did you even know
how to find Nianmato?
I could sense my little
brother's presence here.
Really?
You can do that?
Of course I can!
It's my job to find you.
And I didn't want to overinflate your
ego, so I kept my mouth shut back then.
But you're all grown up now,
so I can shout it out loud!
You're a bona fide bunch of hottie, Yuki!
Wouldn't you two totally agree?
Yep.
Sure do.
Hell yeah!
Sorry about her!
I'll go and get you
something to eat. Big sis!
I know my sister can
be a little unorthodox.
Is it hard working with her?
A little is an understatement.
Yes, but everyone here adores Alba.
Her flaws included.
Whatever you've got
there smells delicious.
We grow these mato mushrooms
in the Hidden Village.
The flavor and aroma are immaculate.
Energizing, too. Mmm.
It smells sweet like fruit juice.
I wonder what ingredients
it would pair well with.
What's wrong?
Oh, dear.
Despite the accident, I take
great pride in my beauty.
Has Nell mesmerized you with her looks?
Are you all right?
Oh, big sis.
Marcus, you brought me
some tasty meat buns!
Time to dig in!
These are just field rations I
swiped from the defense force,
but for now it ought to be...
Mmm, what a nice texture!
I took my eyes off you for two seconds!
Everyone, prepare to depart!
Does that mean you know where Yuki is?
My body began moving automatically,
which implies... It's Yuki!
His transformation must have broken!
I get it!
The price of your ability!
If I have to give him a reward, that makes
me a living, breathing Yuki detector!
Are you feeling a little better now?
Mm-hmm.
I'm so sorry.
Huh?
What is it? Hmm.
It felt like old times for a second there.
The fact that you're actually
sitting next to me finally sunk in.
Oh, I see.
Hey, isn't that a Mato peach?
Uh-huh.
You hadn't eaten one until
after we were separated, right?
Can you blame me?
The procedures and the
paperwork were a headache.
Quite a few people choose not to eat them.
It's just,
well, I had assumed your powers were a
direct result from eating the peaches.
There is a connection between them.
In fact, the truth is, the peaches
are what caused us to look like this.
I want to hear the whole story!
You stay here, Nay.
Keep in contact with HQ for us.
If something should happen,
let me know immediately.
Just leave it to me!
We're a united front. Let's move!
I'm not going to let you go.
I'm not going to work for you,
but I'm not going to work for you!
I'm not going to be a person,
but I'm not going to work for you.
I'm going to get the needle in the ring.
I'm going to get hurt.
I'm going to get you in a chain.
I'm not going to ever leave you.
I'm not going to be left.
Special Defense Forces.
Only women endowed with the benefits
of the peaches are permitted to join.
And aside from combat,
there are other roles too?
Like creating armor out of peach
abilities, like how Ne gathers intel.
It's an extremely difficult job, but it
comes with the honor of rescuing people.
Anyway, next time, we're not on Resight.